Thank you for downloading this script!

This is my script for BHA#3: Unexpected Mastermind 2 contest.

Characters and sprites belong to Zun.
The shot sheet is from Terraformer9x.
The BGM is made by 岩上Crescent: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lWY_7oOE_BY
The DDC Reimu B player is from Ultima.
The cut-in image is from Dairi https://www.pixiv.net/en/artworks/74879384

If anyone credited here wants me to take stuff down, I will do it. 

I hope that you will have fun playing it!

~Kusa